[
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Neil Armstrong becomes the first person to walk on the moon",
    "choice1": "1969",
    "choice2": "1973",
    "choice3": "1977",
    "choice4": "1983",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Christopher Columbus 'discoverd' the New World of the Americas?",
    "choice1": "1201",
    "choice2": "1492",
    "choice3": "1575",
    "choice4": "1699",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Berlin Wall fall?",
    "choice1": "1969",
    "choice2": "1979",
    "choice3": "1989",
    "choice4": "1999",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did the Wright Brothers fly the first powered airplane?",
    "choice1": "1888",
    "choice2": "1903",
    "choice3": "1917",
    "choice4": "1931",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did the Spanish Armada sail attempting to invade England?",
    "choice1": "1347",
    "choice2": "1490",
    "choice3": "1588",
    "choice4": "1702",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did King John sign the Magna Carta?",
    "choice1": "989",
    "choice2": "1074",
    "choice3": "1153",
    "choice4": "1215",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Alexander the Great die in Babylon?",
    "choice1": "476 BC",
    "choice2": "323 BC",
    "choice3": "217 BC",
    "choice4": "138 BC",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did U.S. Civil War begin?",
    "choice1": "1775",
    "choice2": "1799",
    "choice3": "1829",
    "choice4": "1861",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When was Napoleon defeated at the Battle of Waterloo?",
    "choice1": "1793",
    "choice2": "1815",
    "choice3": "1834",
    "choice4": "1858",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Guy Fawkes and others try to blow up the English Parliament?",
    "choice1": "1605",
    "choice2": "1678",
    "choice3": "1719",
    "choice4": "1742",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When was the U.S. Declaration of Independence signed?",
    "choice1": "1694",
    "choice2": "1736",
    "choice3": "1776",
    "choice4": "1814",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Edison patent the light bulb?",
    "choice1": "1879",
    "choice2": "1889",
    "choice3": "1899",
    "choice4": "1909",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did the Black Plague reach Europe?",
    "choice1": "1173",
    "choice2": "1217",
    "choice3": "1269",
    "choice4": "1347",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did the Great Depression start?",
    "choice1": "1920",
    "choice2": "1924",
    "choice3": "1927",
    "choice4": "1929",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "source":"",
    "question": "When did Constantinople fall to Turkish invaders, ending the Byzantine Empire?",
    "choice1": "1412",
    "choice2": "1453",
    "choice3": "1503",
    "choice4": "1549",
    "answer": 2
  }
]